const STORE = {
  questions: [//0
    {
      question: "Are GMO's healthy?",
      options: [
        "yes",
        "no"
      ],
      answer: "no"
    },
    //1
    {
      question: "Does GMO stand for genetically modified organism?",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "yes"
    },
    //2
    {
      question: "GMO's are currently required to be labeled in Europe. Is it currently required in the United States?",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "no"
    },
    //3
    {
      question: "Is there a link between GMO's and infertility?	", 
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "yes"
    },
    //4
    {
      question: "Can GMO's cause digestive problems, fatigue, obesity, clouding of consciousness (brain fog). mood problems/anxiety/depression, food allergies or sensitivities, memory and concentration, Joint pain, seasonal allergies, gluten sensitivities, and insomnia? ",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "yes"
    },
    //5
    {
      question: "Do GMO's mean something is organic?",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "no"
    },
    //6
    {
      question: 'Are GMO health risks just a rumor',
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "no"
    },
    //7
    {
      question: "Are the most common GMO sources from soybean, maze, cotton and canola?", 
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ],
      answer: "yes"
    },
    //8
    {
      question: "Do GMO foods have there genome modified in a way that would otherwise not happen naturally?",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ], 
      answer: "yes"
    },
    //9
    {
      question: "Can GMOs cause make you grow faster?",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ], 
      answer: "no"
    },
    //10
    {
      question: "Should we ban GMO's according to this biased quiz?",
      options: [
          "yes",
          "no"
      ], 
      answer: "yes"
    },
    
  ],
  questionNumber: 0,
  score: 0
};